articlesnare.com 2009-12-30

# Privacy Policy Articles At Article Snare

ArticleSnare.com knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. **By visiting ArticleSnare.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.**

  * What Personal Information About Customers Does ArticleSnare.com Gather?
  * What About Cookies?
  * Does ArticleSnare.com Share the Information It Receives?
  * How Secure Is Information About Me?
  * What About Third-Party Advertisers and Links to Other Web sites.?
  * Which Information Can I Access?
  * What Choices Do I Have?
  * Are Children Allowed to Use ArticleSnare.com?
  * Does ArticleSnare.com Participate in the Safe Harbor Program?
  * Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

**What Personal Information About Customers Does ArticleSnare.com Gather?**

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at ArticleSnare.com. Here are the types of information we gather. 

  * **Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you. 
  * **Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses ArticleSnare.com. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at ArticleSnare.com if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist. 
  * **E-mail Communications:** To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from ArticleSnare.com if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please [email us](http://www.articlesnare.com/pages/Contact-Us.html). 
  * **Information from Other Sources:** We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.

**What About Cookies?**

  * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as greetings. 
  * The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of ArticleSnare.com's coolest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on. 

**Does ArticleSnare.com Share the Information It Receives?**

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only as described below and with subsidiaries ArticleSnare.com controls that either are subject to this Privacy Notice or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Notice. 

  * **Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control:** We work closely with our affiliated businesses. In some cases these businesses operate stores at ArticleSnare.com or sell offerings to you at ArticleSnare.com. In other cases, we operate stores, provide services, or sell product lines jointly with these businesses. You can tell when a third party is involved in your transactions, and we share customer information related to those transactions with that third party. 
  * **Third-Party Service Providers:** We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 
  * **Promotional Offers:** Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of ArticleSnare.com customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please [email us ](http://www.articlesnare.com/pages/Contact-Us.html). 
  * **Business Transfers:** As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that ArticleSnare.com or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets. 
  * **Protection of ArticleSnare.com and Others:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of ArticleSnare.com, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice. 
  * **With Your Consent:** Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information. 

**How Secure Is Information About Me?**

  * We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. 
  * We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. 
  * It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

**What About Third-Party Advertisers and Links to Other Web sites.?**

Our site includes third-party advertising and links to other web sites. We do not provide any personally identifiable customer information to these advertisers or third-party web sites. 

These third-party web sites. and advertisers, or Internet advertising companies working on their behalf, sometimes use technology to send (or "serve") the advertisements that appear on our web site directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third-party web sites. are not covered by this Privacy Notice. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. In addition, the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) offers useful information about Internet advertising companies (also called "ad networks" or "network advertisers"), including information about how to opt-out of their information collection. 

**Which Information Can I Access?**

ArticleSnare.com gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with ArticleSnare.com for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. 

**What Choices Do I Have?**

  * As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of many ArticleSnare.com features.
  * The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. 

**Are Children Allowed to Use ArticleSnare.com?**

ArticleSnare.com does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use ArticleSnare.com only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. 

**Does ArticleSnare.com Participate in the Safe Harbor Program?**

ArticleSnare.com is a participant in the Safe Harbor program developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Union. We have certified that we adhere to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles agreed upon by the U.S. and the E.U. For more information about the Safe Harbor and to view our certification, visit the [U.S. Department of Commerce's Safe Harbor](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/) Web site. If you would like to contact ArticleSnare.com directly about the Safe Harbor program, please send an e-mail to safeharbor@ArticleSnare.com

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**

If you choose to visit ArticleSnare.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the Province of British Columbia. If you have any concern about privacy at ArticleSnare.com, please [contact us](http://www.articlesnare.com/pages/Contact-Us.html) with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it. 

Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.
